准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
Then drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
死敌变亲家
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
裤头村
快逃命啊
Run for it, man
海之霸
好啊  午餐高峰客流
Good, the lunch rush
既然海霸机让你们落入了我的魔掌
Now that my Chumbot has dropped you into my clutches
你们就必须在海之霸用餐
you'll be forced to eat at the Chum Bucket
什么
What?
所以你是想卖快餐才绑架我们的吗
you mean you kidnapped us just to sell us your fast food?
得了吧  这可是标准营销技巧
Come on, it's a standard marketing technique
出口
你这小呆子
You little twerp
他说得对
He's right, you know
厨房
凯伦
Karen
你觉得我是呆子吗
You think I'm a twerp?
没错
Well, yes
但我指的是绑架的事
but I was referring to the kidnapping
在你眼中  我干什么都是错的
Everything I do is always wrong in your eyes
也许是因为你向来都是错的
Maybe it's because you are always wrong
好
Fine--
我都错  你都对
I'm wrong, you're right
你说的  不是我
You said it, not me
我为什么要装上那个唠叨软件
Why did I ever install that nagging software?
唠叨软件
Nagging software?
我都听到了
I heard that
回来帮我屏幕清灰
Come back here and dust my screen
蟹堡王
钱啊
Oh, money
你总是能出手挺我
you're always there for me
你好啊  尤金
Hello, Eugene
老妈
Mother
什么风把你吹来的
What brings you by today?
我只想见见
I just wanted to see
我的宝贝儿子
me favorite son
你想要多少钱
How much of my money do you want?
我今天看到了镇上最漂亮的帽子
Well, I did see the prettiest hat in town today
都这么晚了
Look at the time
抱歉  有急事先走了
So sorry to have to rush off
拜拜
Bye, bye
真是好险啊
That was a close one
我干嘛要买那个电脑老婆
Why did I ever buy that computer wife?
我需要真正的女人
I need a real woman--
不是外表冷漠又强硬的机器女孩
not a girl in a cold, hard shell
好美啊
Such beauty
她就是个天使
She's an angel
还没电线
and no wires
从来没有过这种感觉
I've never felt like this before
我连她名字都不知道
I don't even know her name
她却偷走了我的心
and yet she's stolen my heart
痞老板
Plankton
你又爱上了个另一个女人吗
You've fallen in love with another woman?
我可是你老婆
I'm your wife
你就是个WIFE
You're a W.I.F.E.
线路整合女性化脑电图仪
wired integrated female electroencephalograph
你老用那套话术唬我
You always pull that one out
你才不是真正的老婆
"You're not a real wife
你就只是台电脑
You're just a computer"
你怎么连个关闭按钮都没有
Why don't you have an "off" switch?
关
开
痞老板  你休想
Plankton, don't you dare
来追求那只心爱的生物吧
And now to woo that beloved creature
玫瑰是红的
Roses are red
紫罗兰是蓝的
Violets are blue
统治世界完全比不上你
World domination has nothing on you
估计她不是很喜欢诗歌
I guess she's not a poetry fan
我爱你
诗歌  情书
Poetry, love notes--
全都没用
nothing's working
可能得试试私人点的
Maybe something personal
我真有那么漂亮吗
Am I really that pretty?
好啊
Oh, yeah
我太顺利了
I am smooth
打电话叫她来共进晚餐
Just dial the number and ask her to dinner
加油  你能行的
Come on, you can do this
喂
Hello?
我要挂了
I'm hanging up
别挂
Wait
我是暗恋你的那位
It's your secret admirer
你就是那个巨型机器人啊
You're that giant robot?
不对
No
机器人的程序是我做的
I program the robot
喜不喜欢我送你的礼物
Did you enjoy the gift I sent you?
你怎么知道我想要帽子
How did you know I wanted a hat?
你是不是在监视我
Have you been spying on me?
那个
It was
只是正好猜中而已
just a lucky guess
我已经暗恋你很久了  我的小天使
I've admired you from afar for too long, my angel
一定要来见个面
We must meet face-to-face
要不今晚八点到蟹堡王见面吧
Well, how about the Krusty Krab tonight at 8:00?
一听就不错
Sounds wonderful
到时候戴着红色康乃馨的高个就是我
I'll be the tall fellow wearing a red carnation
今晚见
Until tonight
我的宝贝
my dear
快点  海绵宝宝
Quick, SpongeBob
吞我钱包
swallow me wallet
好
Okay
抱歉  老妈
Sorry, Mommy
没办法让你借钱了
I can't lend you any money
海绵宝宝不小心把我钱包给吞了
SpongeBob accidentally swallowed me wallet
老妈  你没我资助就买了顶帽子
Mommy, you got yourself a hat
without me financial assistance
很棒吧  尤金
Isn't it nice, Eugene?
正好是我想要的
It's just the one I wanted
可是老妈  你不应该乱花我遗产
But, Mommy, you shouldn't be spending my inheritance
我是说  既然你说想要顶帽子
I mean, since you told me you wanted a hat
我就去挖了一顶出来
I went out and dug one up
你上哪找的这种旧货
Where did you get this old thing?
她看着可真安详
She looks so peaceful
是啊  可她先前不是还戴着顶帽子吗
Yeah, but wasn't she wearing a hat?
可以把这玩意扔回垃圾堆了
You can take this back to the trash heap
好的  老妈
Yes, Mommy
章鱼哥  替我去还帽子
Squidward, I need you to make a return for me
多谢你关心我的财务状况
Thank ye for your concern about me finances
但这顶帽子是我新男友给我买的
but me new boyfriend bought me this hat
男朋友
Boyfriend?
有人愿意花钱
Someone to spend money
我是说花时间陪你
I mean, "time" with you?
太美妙了
That's wonderful
他是谁
Who is he?
他叫什么名字
What's his name?
不知道
I don't know
今晚就要在这里跟他见面
I'm meeting him here tonight
太棒了
Wonderful
我会营业到很晚
I'll stay open late
让你能享用美好又浪漫的晚餐
so ye can have a nice, romantic dinner
去吧  打扮得美美的
Run along, make yourself pretty
海绵宝宝  你今晚得加班
SpongeBob, you're working late tonight
不付加班费
No overtime
我今晚预定了两个人的位子
I've reservations for two tonight
这边请  先生
Right this way, sir
不好意思
Excuse me
我够不到银餐具
I can't reach my silverware
万分抱歉  先生
Terribly sorry, sir
还有什么事吗
Will there be anything else?
我领带打直了吗
Is my tie on straight?
可漂亮了
You look fabulous
拜访您的先生已经等候多时
Your gentleman caller awaits
你好  亲爱的
Hello, my dear
不得不说  你今晚美丽动人
I must say you look ravishing tonight
天啊  你个子虽然小
Oh my, you're a tiny thing
但也太可爱了
but awfully cute
介绍一下你自己吧
Tell me about yourself
我是搞餐饮业的
Well, I'm in the food service business
算是个餐厅老板吧
I'm a bit of a restaurateur
我是海之霸的创立者兼老板
I'm the founder and owner of the Chum Bucket
从来没听说过
Never heard of it
就在街对面
It's across the street
没印象
Doesn't ring a bell
就印在电话簿背面
It's on the back of the phone book
海之霸
不吃就去死
真是的  我花了不少广告费呢
Come on, I paid a lot of money for that ad
没关系  没关系
Never mind, never mind
我想听听你的事情
I'd like to hear about you
那个
Well
老痞子
Plankton
老螃蟹
Krabs
尤金
Eugene
老妈
Mommy?
"Mommy"?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
这秀色可餐的生物是你妈
This delectable creature is your mother?
这阴险狡诈的死骗子是你对象
This no-good conniving chiseler is your date?
这位帅哥海绵是你们服务生
And this devilishly handsome sponge is your waiter
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
不知道你在耍什么阴谋诡计  痞老板
I don't know what sort of
skullduggery you're up to, Plankton
我也懒得等着去揭穿
and I'm not waiting to find out
尤金  马上把我男朋友放下来
Eugene, you put me boyfriend down this instant
男朋友
Boyfriend?
可是老妈
But, Mommy
听见她的话了吧
You heard the lady
放我下来
Let me go
这还差不多
That's more like it
来吧  痞老板
Come, Plankton
真抱歉儿子非要搞砸我们的浪漫夜晚
I'm sorry me son had to spoil our romantic evening
老妈
Mommy?
你
You
尤金
Eugene
我来警告你  痞老板
I came to warn you, Plankton
离我妈远点
Stay away from me mother
我知道你有什么打算
I know what you're really up to
我是认真的  尤金
I'm serious, Eugene
我已经洗心革面了
I've changed my ways
都是美女的爱感化了我
And all it took was the love of a beautiful woman
你就只爱小偷小摸
All you love is thieving and conniving
休想借我妈偷到秘方
Now, stop trying to get the formula out of me mother
你胡说什么
What are you talking about?
我说的就是蟹黄堡的秘密配方
I'm talking about the Krabby Patty formula
你妈知道蟹黄堡的秘密配方吗
Your mother knows the Krabby Patty formula?
少给我装傻
Don't play stupid with me
她当然知道了
Of course she does
那可是祖传秘方
It's an old Krabs family recipe
你又不是我家里人
And you're not family
最后再警告你一次
I'm telling you for the last time
离我妈远点
stay away from me mother
不是你家里人吗
Not family, eh?
这我能解决
Well, I can fix that
尤金
Eugene
老妈
Mommy
干涉我私生活的事  我怎么跟你说的
What did I tell ye about interfering in me life?
老妈  你就看不出来吗
Mommy, can't you see?
他这是想从你身上套取蟹黄堡秘方
He's trying to seduce the Krabby Patty formula
right from under you
提醒你一句  尤金
For your information, Eugene
他从来就没有问过我秘方
he hasn't asked me once about the formula
多半还不清楚我知道秘方
I doubt that he even knows that I know it
对
Yeah
这可真奇怪啊
funny thing about that
我禁止你干涉我的私生活
I forbid ye to interfere in me private business
回你办公室去
Go to your office
马上
Now
好  老妈
Yes, Mommy
快给天堂打个电话
Somebody call heaven
好像有位天使失踪了
because I think an angel's gone missing
谢尔顿啊
Oh, Sheldon
蟹太太啊
Oh, Mrs. Krabs
可真是的啊
Oh, brother
大家请注意
Attention, attention, everyone
我宣布个事
I'd like to make an announcement
蟹太太  在全蟹堡王见证之下
Mrs. Krabs, in full view of this restaurant
我请求与你结为婚姻
I ask you for your hand in holy matrimony
你愿意嫁给我吗
Would you marry me?
给我得了
That's it
不能再胆小幼稚地躲在我房间里了
No more hiding in my room like a scared little kid
该来表现成熟点了
It's time to act like a man
求你别嫁给他  老妈
Please don't marry him, Mommy
别嫁给这个大坏蛋啊
Don't marry this bad, bad man
你可千万别啊
I don't want you to
来不及了  小蟹
Too late, Krabsy
我们就快结婚了
We're going to be married
你马上就是我的新儿子了
And you're going to be my new son
怎么了  小甜甜
What's this, honey bunch?
你的赠礼让我受宠若惊
I am flattered by your offer
是真的
Really I am
但我还没准备好做出那样的承诺
But I'm just not ready for that kind of commitment
怎么了
What is this?
是不是还有其他对象
There's somebody else, isn't there?
我
I
太难受了
This is very uncomfortable
我还是在车上等吧
I'll just wait in the car
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this
你骗了我
You led me on
没事  痞老板
Now, now, Plankton
事情不是你想的那样
it's not what ye think
我不想再听你的谎言了
I don't want to hear your lies
你这么骗我  那就欠我一个人情
You owe me for leading me on like this
蟹黄堡秘方给我  就一笔勾销
Give me the Krabby Patty formula, and we'll call it even
秘方
The formula?
所以这才是你的打算吗
Is that what this whole thing was about?
不对  不完全是这样
No, no, not really
至少一开始不是
I mean, not at first
我是说
I mean, uh
小甜甜
Honey bunch?
好吧
Oh, well
曾经深爱过  现在失去了
'tis better to have loved and lost
总比从没爱过好
than never to have loved at all
开
已启动
Working
你总算决定爬回来找我了是吧
So you've decided to come crawling back to me, huh?
你说什么
What did you say?
没什么  老婆
Nothing, dear
我就知道你会那么说  小甜甜
Yeah, that's what I thought you said, honey bunch
美人鱼战士
和企鹅男孩6
大电影
分镜总监
编剧
翻译: 1440kHz
技术总监
动画总监
制片指导
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
客串
配音  美人鱼战士
配音  企鹅男孩
是美人鱼战士
It's Mermaidman
深海的救星
Savior of the deep
与他的年轻得力助手  企鹅男孩
And his young, fit servant, Barnacleboy
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
合为一体
unite
海草怪  这里明令禁止停船
Kelp-Thing, this is a posted no-parking zone
但我非要干这行不可
But I must do what I do
拖离
坏蛋早六到晚十二禁止在这停船
Evil can't park here
between the hours of 6:00 a.m. and 12:00 p.m.
本集完
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
粉丝俱乐部
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
粉丝俱乐部成员
Fan Club members
合为一体
unite
Unite
现在是第二项要务
And now, the second order of business
德瑞皮兄弟制片厂目前正在拍摄
Drippy Brothers Studios is currently in production
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩大电影
on the Mermaidman and Barnacleboy movie
天啊  派大星
Oh, boy, Patrick
我等不及要看我们最爱的英雄
I can hardly wait to see our favorite heroes
登上大银幕了
on the big screen
第三项要务  特别惊喜嘉宾
Third order of business, the special surprise guest
美人鱼战士大电影的主演明星
The stars of the Mermaidman movie
今晚到场了
are here tonight
现在他们从片场过来了
Directly from the set, here they are
小英雄们好
Hello, little heroes
你们不是美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
You're not Mermaidman and Barnacleboy
你们是冒牌货
You're fakes
当然假了
Well, of course we are--
我们可是演员
we're actors
演员
Actors?
拍美人鱼战士大电影怎么可以
How can you make a Mermaidman movie
不找真正的美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩
without the real Mermaidman and Barnacleboy?
小子听好  这可是动作大片
Listen, kid, this is an action movie
你们的过气英雄太老了  没法打斗
Your has-been heroes are too old for action
美人鱼战士永垂不朽
Mermaidman is timeless
没错
Yeah
我站在这里为大家说出心声
I think I speak for everyone here
我认为大家绝对不会支持
when I say we won't stand
那两个冒牌货
for these two phony baloneys
毁掉我们英雄的好名声
ruining the good name of our heroes
凡是有正义感的
No right-minded
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩社社员
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy society member
都不会花钱看这部
would ever pay to see this
这部烂片
this celluloid hoax
我提议抵制这部电影
I say we boycott this movie
谁挺我
Now who's with me?
裤头村活动中心
叛徒
Traitors
就等我们跟美人鱼战士说这件事好了
Wait till we tell Mermaidman about this
荫凉滩疗养院
B47
B-47
帮扣
Bonko
应该说  宾果
It's "Bingo"
你手别碰我  女的
Get your hands off me, woman
宾果
A29
A-29
太老了  演不了动作片
Too old for an action movie
这次又怎么了  小子
What is it this time, kid?
你们就不知道德瑞皮兄弟制片厂在拍
Are you aware that Drippy Brothers Studios is making
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩大电影吗
the Mermaidman and Barnacleboy movie?
他们不可能会拍我们的电影
They can't be making a movie about us
可他们真拍了
But they are
而且还用了
And they're using
演员
actors
他们有意回避了我们的英雄
They have shunned our heroes
而且也对他们不是很友善
And they weren't nice to them either
这下我们登上大银幕的梦想
Now our dreams of being big-screen heroes
再也没法实现了
will never come true
这样就更严重了
Well, that makes it even worse
最好是这样  小子
You bet it does, kid
最严重的就是
And the worst part is
我忘了我干嘛要哭了
I can't remember why I started crying
不然我们自制一部电影吧
Why don't we just make our own movie?
派大星  你的才能又发光发热了
Patrick, once again you have exposed your brilliance
就拍一部真正的
We'll make a real
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩大电影
Mermaidman and Barnacleboy movie
就在荫凉滩这里拍
Right here at Shady Shoals
真的吗
You will?
没错
Yes
这样就能帮你们拨乱反正
And in doing so, we will right the wrong done to you
纠正邪恶的德瑞皮兄弟制片厂和
by the evil Drippy Brothers Studios and
他们的演员
their actors
平反是我们的责任
Vindication is ours
平
Vindi
我怎么上来的
How did I get up here?
蟹堡王
派大星  电影一开始需要什么东西
Okay, Patrick, what do we need to start a movie?
爆米花吗
Popcorn?
不对  派大星
No, Patrick
我问的是拍电影
to start making a movie
来先定下
Let's start with
标题
the title
好  好
Yeah, yeah
我想到了
I got one
地下城历险记
"Adventures in the Underground City"
很好  派大星
Great, Pat
有啥情节
What happens?
有这么一座城
Well, there's a city
城
City
就在地下
and it's underground
地下
Underground
主角展开了历险记
and they have an adventure
历险记
Adventure
剧终
The end
终
End
非常棒  派大星
That's great, Pat
好像有点短了
Seems kinda short
我有个办法
I have an idea
让它变长一点
Let's make it longer
变长  好啊
Longer, yes
那就让美人鱼战士
Okay, let's have Mermaidman
脸被海草怪的脸部缩小机缩小
get his face shrunk by Kelp-Thing's face minimizer
好  然后他
Yeah, and then he, um
他喝了
he drinks
芝士咖啡
cheese coffee
真好笑  派大星
Good one, Pat
你们几个在干什么
What are ye lads doing?
我们在拍电影
We're making a movie
好啊
Great
我正好有最新兴的影星
I got cinema's newest star right here
你说怎么样  小子
What do you say, lad?
好啊  蟹老板
Sure, Mr. Krabs
珍珍可以来参演
Pearl can be in our movie
我说的不是珍珍
I wasn't talking about Pearl
我说的是蟹黄堡
I was talking about the Krabby Patty
你也可以参演  珍珍
You can be in it, too, Pearl
我要变成影星了
I'm going to be a movie star
来认识一下技艺高超的专家
Let's meet the highly skilled professionals
他们可以帮忙实现
who will help us fulfill
你登上大银幕的梦想
your dream of being on the big screen
珊迪负责特技和爆炸场面
Sandy will handle the stunts and explosives
大家好
Howdy
珍珍是女主演
Pearl is the leading lady
蟹老板为摄制提供餐饮
Mr. Krabs will cater the affair
派大星负责摄影
Patrick will run the camera
这位是章鱼哥
This is Squidward
他负责化妆组
He's in charge of the makeup department
不用了
No, thanks
谁想当什么化妆组
Who wants to be the "makeup department"?
不是化妆组  你当的是化妆艺术家
Not makeup department, you're the makeup artist
艺术家
Artist?
化妆艺术家
Makeup artist
那我就来把演员化得美美的
In that case, let's make those old crabapples sizzle
艺术家要来创造美了
Time for the art-eest to go to work
看吧
Voilà
大家请就位
Okay, places, everybody
章鱼哥  主角准备好了吗
Squidward, are our heroes ready?
好得不能再好了
As they'll ever be
他们好漂亮
They're beautiful
就跟三十年前一个样
They look just like they did 30 years ago
好  开拍
Okay, action
我爱我的新工作
I love my new job
干得漂亮  珊迪
Good job, Sandy
我  射线恶魔
I, Man Ray
自黑暗深渊回归
have returned from the murky depths
报仇雪恨  并将你们的灵魂
to seek my revenge and banish your souls
放逐至下界
to the nether regions
他们的防御力虽强
Their defenses are strong
但是敌不过我的射线恶魔射线
But they're no match for my Man-Ray ray
你在干什么
What are you doing?
海绵宝宝  这角色是为我量身打造的
SpongeBob, this role was made for me
可这电影都没射线恶魔戏份
That villain isn't even in this movie
不过还是先看有啥活
But let me see if we have something
可以符合你的条件吧
that fits your qualifications
来活儿了
Here's something
你可以当杆爷来现场收音
You can be the boom operator
我以为珊迪就是杆爷
I thought Sandy was the boom operator
炸
有谁说到爆炸了吗
Did somebody say "boom"?
好了  海绵宝宝
All right, SpongeBob
你这可是白瞎了我的才华
But you're squandering my talents
派大星  开始拍摄
Okay, Patrick, start the movie
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩大电影
第一次拍摄
Take one
一定要夺回那些失节的蟹黄堡
We have to get back those swollen Krabby Patties
停
Cut
不对  美人鱼战士
No, Mermaidman
是  失窃的蟹黄堡
it's "stolen Krabby Patties"
第二次拍摄
Take Two
一定要夺回
We have to get back
那些失窃的蟹房包去
to those stolen maggie daddies
停
Cut
不对  美人鱼战士
No, Mermaidman
是  失窃的蟹黄堡
it's "stolen Krabby Patties"
第5003次拍摄
Take 5,003
一定要夺回那些失窃的蟹黄堡
We have to get back those stolen Krabby Patties
要是不阻止那个可恶的坏蛋
And if we don't stop that diabolical scoundrel
还回来
Give it back
果然是个馊主意
I knew this was a bad idea
停
Cut
痞老板  下次
Plankton, next time
可不可以别让麦入镜
could you keep the boom out of the shot?
除此之外  你的工作非常出色
Other than that, you're doing a super job
太丢脸了
This is humiliating
我根本就不擅长当杆爷
I'm not good at this boom thing
炸
有谁说到爆炸了吗
Did somebody say "boom"?
老爸
Oh, Daddy
你说我会变明星的
you said I was going to be a star
没错  珍珍
You are, Pearl
美人鱼战士没你  哪都去不了
Mermaidman wouldn't get anywhere without you
快上场吧  加油
Go out there and break a leg
好耶
Yeah
好  开拍
Okay, action
海草怪藏身处
前往无影船
To the boatmobile
上音效
Cue sound effects
听听这发动机突的
Listen to that engine purr
就快到了
Almost there
早安  海绵宝宝
Good morning, SpongeBob
全都毁了
Everything's ruined
至少拍到了画面
Well, at least we got the footage
对  我拍到了画面
Yeah, I got the footage
派大星  那是什么
Patrick, what is that?
是摄影机
It's a camera
不对  派大星
No, Patrick
这个
this
是镜头盖
That's a lens cap
你刚把它给盖上去了吗
Did you just put that on?
没有  我不想弄丢它
No, I didn't want to lose it
所以拍摄前我就盖上去了
so I put it there right before we started filming
电影全毁了
The movie's ruined
拍不了电影了
We can't make a movie
小英雄
Hey, little hero
这让我想起了第912集
this reminds me of Episode 912
我们那时被包围了
We were surrounded
海草怪就在我们右边
The Kelp-Thing was to our right
旁边还有西兰花
and there was broccoli on the side
但是假如有我唯一记得的事情
But if there's one thing I remember
那这件事就是遗忘
it's how to forget
派大星  时机正好
Patrick, this is good
开始拍摄
Roll the film
吃葡萄不吐葡萄
The rain in Spain stays mainly on the
辟
Space
最后倒计时
The final countdown
要坚持那个
Stick to the
坚持那个
stick to the
我亲爱的卢啊
Lou, my darling
卢
Lou
快去把电影拍完  小子
Now get out there and finish this movie, kid
电影首映
蟹老板  你哭什么啊
Mr. Krabs, why are you weeping?
我特地提早打烊来放你的电影
I closed early for your movie
花钱的客人呢
Where are the paying customers?
你说好会座无虚席的
You promised a full house
客人来就座了
And here comes the filling
美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩粉丝俱乐部
The Mermaidman and Barnacleboy Fan Club
我就知道你们会来看
I knew you'd come see
真正的美人鱼战士和企鹅男孩大电影
the real Mermaidman and Barnacleboy movie
其实真电影的票卖完了
Actually, the real movie was sold out
我要买两百张票
I'll take 200 tickets, please
这才叫美好结局嘛
Now, this is what I call a happy ending
真
美人鱼战士
和企鹅男孩
大电影
重要时刻到来了  我们登上大银幕了
Well, our big moment, us up on the big screen
罗克斯
罗克斯堡
Fort Lox
五十多亿蟹黄堡的家
home to over five billion Krabby Patties
什么样的邪恶天才敢潜入这铜墙铁壁
What evil mastermind
would dare infiltrate this fortified fort
拐走里面的财宝
and make off with its treasure?
就是我
It is I
海草怪
Kelp-Thing
非干不可
Do what I do
住手
Stop
你不能那样
You can't do that
禁止了
Forbidden
看我
Watch me
准备好感受我的怒火吧
Prepare to feel my wrath
你这恶棍
you foul villain
虽然你可能还是成功偷到了蟹黄堡
You may have won the Krabby Patties
但是战斗仍要继续
but the battle rages on
美人鱼战士
Mermaidman
鹅男孩
nacleboy
合为一体
unite
剧终
小子  你向全世界证明了
Well, kid, you showed the world
虽然我们的步伐慢了下来
that even though our steps may have been slowed
但我们这把英雄老骨头还是能打的
we still have a little action left
in these heroic old bones
至少能打一点点
Well, at least some of them